텅 빈 박스야
Completely empty box.
한번 확인해봐
If you'd like to examine it...
Mm-hmm. Yep.
헛된 어린 시절
말고는 없네
I see nothing in this box
but a wasted childhood.
첼로 학원이나
다닌 주제에
Little snarky there,
Cello Lessons.
평범한 원통이야
And we have this completely
ordinary cylinder.
살펴보시지
If you'd like to examine it...
평범하지만
신비로운 기운이 느껴져
Ordinary, yet I sense it is
dripping with magical potential.
세상에
Oh, dear Lord.
장을 비우려고
잠시 떠난 사이
A man pops out for a moment
to evacuate his bowels
배트맨 만화책도
좀 읽고 말야
and catch up on the adventures
of the Caped Crusader,
돌아오니 웬 카바레에
온 것 같네
only to emerge
and discover his apartment
has been transformed
into a cabaret.
사촌 생일 파티 전에
리허설을 하는 중이야
Sheldon, he's just
practicing for his
cousin's birthday party.
계속할게
As I was saying...
텅 빈 박스에
텅 빈 원통
empty box, empty cylinder,
and... ooh!
짜잔
(whispers): Voila.
호그와트행 기차에
네 자리도 있을 거야
I'm telling you, dude,
there's a seat
on the Hogwarts Express
with your name on it.
사촌 앞에서
이런 짓이나 한다고?
This is how you're
going to entertain
your little cousin
and his friends?
애들을 속이는 거잖아
By lying to them?
속이는 거라니?
(chuckles): How is this lying?
마술 자체가
기만적인 행위야
A magic show is an inherently
deceitful proposition.
'이것은 평범한 모자입니다'
"This is an ordinary top hat."
'아무 카드나 뽑아봤습니다'
"You've chosen
that card freely."
'자물쇠 해제 장치를
엉덩이에 숨기지 않았어요'
"I do not have a set of lock
picks lodged in my keister."
그냥 즐기면 안돼?
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Can't you
just enjoy the wonder, Sheldon?
왜 커튼 뒤를
훔쳐보려고 해?
Why must you
peek behind the curtain?
똥구멍까지 파헤치지 말자
Or up the butt?
모자 속에서
토끼가 나온다면서
If we poison the critical
thinking faculties of children
아이들의 비판적
사고법을 해치면
by telling them that rabbits
어른이 되서도
점성술과 동종요법을 믿겠지
come out of hats,
then we create adults
who believe in astrology
and homeopathy
'그린 랜턴'에
라이언 레이놀즈가
and that Ryan Reynolds was a
better choice for Green Lantern
나단 필리온보다
더 어울린다고 생각할걸
than lovable rogue
Nathan Fillion.
쉘든
Sheldon,
마술을 보여주는 것 뿐이야
he's just gonna do a few
magic tricks for some kids.
설마 '그린 랜턴'을
즐겨보게 될까?
I really don't think
they're gonna end up
liking the Green Lantern movie.
너무 몰아붙이지 마
Don't be so
hard on him.
쉽게 짜증 낼 법도 해
It's natural to be
a little cranky when you have...
귓속에 동전이 있거든
(grunts): a quarter
in your ear!
신체 부위에 동전이
나오는 건 웃을 일이 아냐
Coins lodged in body parts
is not a source of amusement.
5살 때는 빌리가
페소 동전을 내 코에 넣었어
When I was five, Billy Sparks
put a Mexican peso up my nose.
(laughter)
그게 어째서 안 웃기지?
Wait-wait-wait,
how is that not amusing?
아직도 있어
It's still there.
공항 보안을 통과하려면
45분이나 걸린다고
Takes me
45 minutes to get
through airport security.
쉘든을 사라지게 했어,
어때?
Look, I made
Sheldon disappear. Ta-da.
다음에는 제일 먼저 하도록
Next time, you should
open with that.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x12
The Shiny Trinket Maneuver
Original Air Date on January 12, 2012
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
이게 누구야,
데이트하러 왔네
Ooh, look who's out on a date.
패서디나의 인기 커플,
쉐이미
Pasadena's favorite
power couple, Shamy.
아까 물어본 질문에
대한 답이 나왔네
And that is the answer
to the question,
왜 치즈케이크 팩토리에서
먹으면 안 되는가
what is wrong with eating
at The Cheesecake Factory?
오늘 무슨 특별한 날이야?
So, are we celebrating
anything special tonight?
물론이지
Oh, yes.
연애 계약서에 의하면
Our relationship
agreement specifies
매달 둘째 목요일
that the second Thursday
of every month,
5주가 있다면
셋째 목요일이
or the third Thursday
in a month with five Thursdays,
데이트하는 날이야
is date night.
완전 멋지다
That is so hot.
지난 번 데이트에 논의된
사항은 의결되었다 치고
All right, without objection,
the minutes of the previous date
are considered
read and agreed to.
새로 보고할 일 있어?
Any new business?
오늘 하루 어땠어?
How was your day?
최고였어
Superb.
아침에 알파벳 씨리얼로
회문을 만들었어
This morning I made
a palindrome
with my Alpha-Bits.
"Nice hat, Bob Tahecin."
좋은 시작이네
Sounds like you
hit the ground running.
나도 좋은 소식이 있어
I have a bit of
good news myself.
장기 증강으로 인한
My most recent paper
수상돌기가지의
메모리 시퀀스 매핑법 논문이
on how a cooperative
long-term potentiation
can map memory sequences
in dendritic branches
'뉴런' 표지로 채택되었어
made the cover of Neuron.
좋은 소식은 나도 있는데
Ooh! Speaking of good news,
somebody...
트위터 팔로워가
100명으로 늘었어
just hit 100
Twitter followers.
좋겠네
That's nice.
암튼 난 이런 날이
오길 기다렸어
Anyway, I've been
dreaming of this day
나도 마찬가지야
for a long time.
Yeah, me, too.
3자리 숫자잖아
Triple digits,
I'm not gonna lie--
기분 째지네
it feels pretty good.
쉘든
Sheldon,
내가 혼자 쓴 논문이
저명 저널에 게재됐어
I'm the sole author
on a paper being published
in a distinguished journal
that may change
내 분야에서 알아 준다고
the course of my field.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
오, 101명이나 됐다
Ooh, 101!
산소가 모자랄 정도야
Air's getting
a bit thin up here.
산소가 모자랄 정도야주문 받을까?
So, are we ready to order?
잠시만
Give me a minute.
씻고 올게
I'm gonna go wash up.
이상하네
Well, that's odd.
들어왔을 때 이미 씻었는데
We both washed up
when we came in.
소변을 완곡하게
표현했나보군
It's probably a euphemism
for urination.
쉘든, 넌 뭐가 문제니?
Sheldon, what is
wrong with you?
별 문제 없어
Not much. Although,
I can be faulted
코알라를 지나치게
좋아한다는 것 빼고는
for being overly fond
of koala bears.
이유는 잘 모르지만
I don't know what it is,
유칼립투스를
씹고 있는 모습을 보면
when they smart munching
on eucalyptus,
마음이 따뜻해져
I just melt inside.
에이미가 방금
중요한 얘기를 했는데
Okay, Amy just told you
some exciting news,
넌 아무렇지도 않게
넘어갔잖아
and you acted like
it was no big deal.
네가 왜 그러는지 알겠다
Oh, I see why you're confused.
중요하게 들릴 수도 있는데
No, her news sounded important,
but what you're forgetting is,
생물학 관련 업적이잖아
it was an achievement
in the field of biology.
징그럽고 질척한 것들 말이야
That's all about yucky,
squishy things.
에이미가 속상해하잖아
Honey, she's upset.
You're her boyfriend.
남자친구로서
기쁜 척이라도 해야지
You have to at least
try to be excited
by the things
she's excited by.
난 전혀 신이 안 나는걸
What if they simply
don't excite me?
웃으면서 코알라 생각을 해
Well, just smile and
think about koalas.
너무 티가 날걸
She'd see right through that.
동물원에 자주 가서
We go to the zoo all the time.
코알라 표정은 다 읽힐 거야
She knows my koala face.
너도 참고할 수 있게 보여줄게
And for future reference,
it's this.
마술 용품이 많네
Oh, you have a lot
of magic stuff.
응
Yeah.
10대부터 시작했어
I started when I was a teenager.
여자들한테
마술을 보여주면서
I thought I could show
a girl a few tricks
방에 와서 나머지를
감상하라고 꼬셨지
and invite her up to my bedroom
to see the rest of the act.
효과는 있었어?
Did it work?
힘을 발휘한 지팡이라고는
이것 밖에 없지
Ah, let's just say the only wand
that ever saw any action
was this one.
엄마가 공연 의상을
만들어줬어
Oh, look what my mom
made us for the act.
Ooh...
천이 마음에 든다
I like the fabric.
어디서 구했어?
Where'd she get it?
전에 입던 수영복으로
만들었나봐
Well, she cut up one
of her old bathing suits.
조끼 2벌이랑
냅킨 여러 장이 나왔지
She made these two vests
and half a dozen napkins.
조끼는 입어봤니?
MRS. WOLOWITZ (calls): Has she
tried on the vest yet?!
방금 줬어요
I just gave it to her!
잘 맞았으면 좋겠네,
몸매가 좀 까다롭잖니
I hope it fits-- she
has a tricky figure!
작지만 풍만하잖아,
나처럼
She's short
and stacked, like me!
엄마처럼은 아니거든요,
자기 것을 밟은 적 없어요
She's not stacked like you, Ma!
She never steps on hers!
어쩌면 난 도우미로
적합하지 않을 것 같아
Listen, Howie,
maybe I'm not the best choice
to be a magician's assistant.
잘 할 수 있어,
거기 링 좀 줘봐
You'll do fine.
Hand me those rings?
봤지?
잘 하네
See? You nailed it.
난 아이들이 불편해서 그래
You know, i-it's just that
I'm not that comfortable
with little kids.
경험이 없어서 그럴 거야
Well, that's because you
haven't been around them much.
연습으로 삼으면 되지
This is good
practice. I mean,
넌 엄마가 될 거잖아
you are gonna be
a mom someday, right?
Mmm...
Yeah, sure.
Oh-ho-ho!
이건 정말 오랜만에 본다
I haven't seen
this trick in years.
비둘기 냄비야
It's called
the dove pan.
관객에게 비어있는
냄비를 보여주는데
You let everyone see
the pan is empty,
뚜껑에 비밀 공간이 있어
but there's a secret
compartment in the lid.
뚜껑을 열면 살아있는...
And then you open it
and produce a live...
저쪽은 가만히 두자
Don't look in there.
'레드 데드 리뎀션'이네
Oh, a little Red
Dead Redemption, huh?
응
SHELDON:
Yes.
왜 미션을 안 해?
How come you're not
doing a mission?
혼자 돌아다니기만 하네
You're just
wandering around.
피곤한 하루였어
Had a rough night.
산책이나 하면서
머리 좀 식히려고
I thought I'd go for a walk
and clear my head.
어떤 사람들은
실제로 밖에 나가던데
Some people go outside
and do that.
9시 지났잖아,
패서디나에서 이 시간에는
It's after 9:00-- at this hour
the streets of Pasadena
주정뱅이랑 길고양이 밖에 없어
are teeming with drunken sailors
and alley cats.
얘기 좀 들어줄까?
You want to talk about it?
아니
No.
그냥 바에 들어가서
술이나 퍼마셔야지
I think I'll just go
in this saloon
and drink my troubles away.
디지털 알코올은 해결책이 아냐
You know digital
alcohol is never a solution.
무슨 일이야?
What's going on?
(sighs)
믿기 어렵겠지만
Hard as this may be to believe,
난 좋은 남자친구가
아닐 수 있어
it's possible that
I'm not boyfriend material.
내가 앉아 있을 때
발표를 해줘서 다행이야
Glad I was sitting down
for that.
에이미랑 싸웠어?
Did you and Amy get in a fight?
나는 논리적이였는데
에이미가 삐졌지
Amy had a fight; I was being
perfectly reasonable.
난 위스키 마실래
I'm gonna have a whiskey.
너도 뭐 마실래?
Do you want anything?
난 안돼
No, I can't.
Grand Theft Auto를 할 거라
I'm playing Grand
Theft Auto later.
이봐, 나도 여자를
잘 모르지만
Look, I'm no expert in women...
그걸 말이라고 해?
I'll say.
도와주려고 하는데 그래야겠어?
That's not necessary when
someone's trying to help you.
미안해, 취했나봐
I'm sorry.
It's the alcohol talking.
계속해
Go on.
가끔은 여자의 얘기를 들어주고
Sometimes with women you want
to listen to what upsets them
너도 노력할 거라는
믿음을 줘야해
and then show them
that you can grow and change.
그거 말고는 없어?
Nuts to that.
What else you got?
선물이라도 주던가
Buy her something.
그건 어떻게 먹히는데?
How does that work?
감정적인 부분을 배제하고
Well, you skip over
any attempt to repair
투자를 해서
기분을 풀어주는 거지
your emotional connection
and you win back her affection
with an empty financial gesture.
완전 내 스타일이네
Well, that approach has Sheldon
Cooper written all over it.
도움이 됐다니 뿌듯하다
Glad I could help.
고마워
It's appreciated.
And if you ever manage
너도 여자가 생기는
날이 온다면 꼭 보답할게
to find a woman again, I'll
be glad to return the favor.
이제 모든 링이 연결되었다
And now, all
the rings are
magically linked together.
내 약혼자도
매직 링을 끼고 있어
My fiancee's wearing
a magic ring, too.
저걸 사느라
돈이 다 사라졌거든
It made all my money disappear.
Oh, ah, right.
다음 순서는
하우디니의 일루전입니다
And now, the
great Howdini's
next miraculous
illusion.
케이크는 언제 먹어요?
When are we gonna have cake?
완전히 놀란 다음에 먹자
After you've
been thoroughly amazed.
지금 먹고 싶어요
But we want cake now.
지금은 안 된다니까
Well, you're not getting cake
right now, capisce?
(chuckles):
Okay. Okay.
이제 저의 아름다운 도우미가
Now, my lovely assistant
is going to bring me
평범한 우유 피처를
갖고 올 겁니다
an ordinary
pitcher of milk.
그거 어떻게 하는지 알아요
I know how you do that trick.
입은 다물 줄 아니?
Do you know how to pipe down?
신문지를 돌돌 말고
(chuckles):
Okay, we're going
to roll up
this newspaper.
가짜 피처잖아요
It's a fake pitcher.
귀가 잘 안 들리니?
You got wax in your ears?
평범한 피처라고 했잖아
The man said
it's an ordinary pitcher.
하우디니
Howdini.
신문지를 고정하고
Okay, we're going
to stick this in here.
우유를 부을 거야
And then I'm going
to pour in the milk.
꼭 성공해야 할 텐데
(chuckles):
I hope this works,
갈아입을 바지도 없어
because I didn't
bring a change of pants.
구글에 검색했어요
Look, I Googled it.
가짜 피처라고요
It's a fake pitcher.
못 참겠다
That's it.
넌 이제 케이크 못 먹어
No cake for you.
또 케이크
먹기 싫은 사람 있어?
Anyone else want to
join the No Cake Club?
농담이야, 얘들아
She's just kidding,
boys and girls.
다 같이 케이크 먹자
Everyone gets cake.
쟤 빼고
Not him.
피처나 줘봐
Just give me the pitcher.
(clears throat)
짜잔!
Behold!
(laughter)
잘못 갖고 왔네
Wrong pitcher.
아이들 잘 못
다룬다고 했잖아
I told you I'm not
good with kids.
그랬지
Yes, you did.
가랑이가 응고되는 느낌이야
Oh, I think my crotch
is starting to curdle.
엄마가 일 때문에 바빠서
The thing is, my mother
worked full-time.
동생들을 돌봐야 했어
I had to take care of
my brothers and sisters.
그런데?
Yeah, so?
끔찍했어
Ugh, it was horrible!
코딱지에 똥 묻은 기저귀
With their snotty noses
and their poopy diapers
항상 불평만 하잖아
and their little shrieky voices,
always complaining.
'옷 입기 싫어'
"I don't want to get dressed."
'조이가 입에 침을 뱉어'
"Joey keeps spitting
in my mouth."
'엄마가 만든 와플이랑 달라'
"This isn't the way
Mom makes waffles."
손을 와플기에 집어 넣어!
(yelling): Well, okay, put your
hand in here.
이 와플은
무슨 맛인지 볼까?
Let's see how you
like this waffle!
침착해
All right, settle down.
빨간 불이야
Red light.
빨간 불이라고
Red light, red light!
휴, 살았다
Okay, we're fine.
미안해
I'm sorry.
나쁘게 들리겠지만
I know it makes me sound
like a bad person,
난 애들이 싫어
but I just don't like children.
충분히 알아들었어
Yeah, no, we all got that.
우리 아이면 다르지 않을까?
But don't you think
it'll be different
when the child is ours?
내 몸을 망치고
밤새 보채고
Right, when it's our kid
that's ruined my body
미래도 직장도 없어지고
and kept me up all night and
I've got no career and no future
적어도 20년 동안 고생할 텐데
and nothing to be happy about
for the next 20 years,
완전히 다르겠지
sure, that'll be
completely different.
Well, yeah.
여기는 에이미가 좋아할
물건이 하나도 없어
I don't think there's
anything in this jewelry store
시어스 백화점에서 봤던
가습기가 제일 낫다
that Amy would appreciate more
than the humidifier we were
just looking at at Sears.
내가 멍청한 소리를 할 때
이런 기분이 들겠군
Oh, my God, now I know
what I sound like to you
when I say stupid stuff.
회중시계네
Ooh, a pocket watch.
그런 걸 원하지는 않을 거야
Okay, I don't think Amy
wants a pocket watch.
회중시계를 가진
남자를 원할 수도
No, but maybe she wants
a man with a pocket watch.
멍청한 소리 좀 그만해
Still saying stupid stuff.
Ooh...
팔찌는 좋아해?
Does she like bracelets?
'페니실린 알레르기'라고 적힌
은팔찌는 좋아하더라
Well, she's very fond
of her silver one
that says "allergic
to penicillin."
그것보다 좀 화려한 거 없을까?
Maybe they have a dressier
version of that?
어떻게 도와드릴까요?
Well, how are we doing
this afternoon?
특별한 거 찾으시나요?
Are we looking for
anything special?
여자친구 반지는 어떠세요?
Perhaps a ring for the lady?
저희는 절대 커플이 아닙니다
(snorts) Trust me, we are
not a couple.
저기
Excuse me.
그렇게 콧방귀를 뀌다니
I don't see why you get to snort
derisively and point that out.
나랑 사귈 수만 있다면
네 행운인 줄 알아
You'd be lucky to land
a fella like me.
맘대로 생각해
Fine, go ahead.
저희는 절대 커플이 아닙니다
(snorts) Trust me, we are
not a couple.
실례를 했군요
My apologies.
그럼 어떻게 도와드릴까요?
How can I help you today?
여자친구랑 문제가 생겨서
선물을 사려고 해요
He's in trouble
with his girlfriend
and needs to
buy her a present.
여자친구와 생긴 문제 덕분에
Great, trouble with girlfriends
우리 딸 등록금을 댈 수 있어요
is what's putting
my daughter through USC.
진짜 다이아몬드인가요?
Ooh, are these real diamonds?
20포인트 바게트 다이아입니다
Yes. Channel set baguettes,
20 points total weight.
놀랍군요
Remarkable.
크리스탈 형태의
탄소 덩어리인데
Diamonds, crystallized carbon.
사람들은 매일 마트에 가서
Every day, people go
to the grocery store
탄소의 다른 형태인
숯을 사오고
and come home with
sacks full of carbon
in the form of
charcoal briquettes
바베큐를 한다며
불에 던져 넣는데
that they toss in their
barbeques and set on fire.
탄소 원자가
잘 정리되었다고
But just because
you've got some carbon
with the atoms stacked neatly,
몇 천 달러나 내라고요?
you expect me to plunk down
thousands of dollars.
$750 밖에 안해요
Actually, that's only 750.
세일 중이라서요
Everything's on sale.
아까 저 회중시계도
보여주세요
Really. Talk to me
about that pocket watch.
아직 받아들이기 어렵다
I'm still trying to
wrap my mind around it.
언젠가는 아빠가
될 줄 알았거든
I always
thought I'd be a dad someday.
나도 그래
Oh, me, too.
넌 다정하잖아
You're so caring.
아들을 훌륭한 남자로
키워낼 것 같았는데
I've often pictured you guiding
a young boy into manhood.
해결됐네, 하워드
There you go, Howard.
라지랑 낳으면 되겠다
Sounds like Raj'll have
your babies; problem solved.
남자가 다른 남자에게
관심을 보인다 해서
Hey, just because a man
shows caring for another man
금지된 사랑이란
법은 없잖아
doesn't mean he's
displaying the love
that dare not speak its name.
진짜 안 키운다고 했어?
Did she definitely say
she didn't want kids?
애들을 싫어한대
Yeah, she doesn't like them.
내가 본 바로는
서로 싫어하더군
And from what I saw,
the feeling was mutual.
그럼 어떻게 할 거야?
What are you gonna do?
모르겠어
I don't know.
아이를 없는 미래는
상상한 적 없어
I can't see a life
where I don't have kids.
누구나 다 아이를 갖잖아
I mean, people have kids.
게임 캐릭터 동키콩도
동키콩 주니어가 있었어
I mean, even Donkey Kong
had Donkey Kong Jr.
공주를 납치하고 나무통을
던지는 법도 가르쳐줬다고
So he could teach someone
how to kidnap princesses
and throw barrels
at Italian plumbers.
아이가 생긴다고 해서
좋아할 거라는 보장은 없어
You know, there's no guarantee
even if you have kids
that you're going to like them.
그건 또 어디서
나온 생각이야?
Wow, that's rough.
Where'd you get that?
엄마가 최근에 쓴
책에서 나왔어
It's right off the dust jacket
of my mom's last book.
나랑 베르나데트는
잘 안 맞나봐
Maybe me and Bernadette
aren't right for each other.
바닷가에는
물고기가 많긴 한데
Look, Howard, I'd say there's
a lot of fish in the sea,
넌 몇 년 동안
물 속에서 수확이 없었어
but I watched you dangle your
hook in the water for years.
절대 놔주지 마
Do not throw her back.
나도 그러고 싶지 않은데
이건 좀 아냐
I don't want to, but this is
kind of a deal breaker.
결혼을 취소하면
너네 엄마가 뭐라할까?
What's your mom going to say
if you call off the wedding?
실망하시겠지
Oh, it'll kill her.
손주를 못 봐도
실망이 크겠지만
On the other hand, if I don't
give her grandchildren,
that'll kill her, too.
어찌됐든 불효를
하게 되겠군
So, either way,
on the Mom front, I'm golden.
에이미한테
몇 시에 오라 했어?
What time did you tell
Amy to be here?
8시
8:00.
회중시계는 좀 아니다
Sheldon, that pocket watch
is ridiculous.
무슨 소리야
Nonsense.
기관사처럼 보이잖아
I look like a train conductor.
에이미한테는
뭐라고 한 거야?
Under what pretext
did you lure her here?
그냥 우리 집에서 놀자고 했지
(knocking) I said, "Hey, want
to come over and hang out?"
다행이다,
뭔가 거창하게 꾸몄다면
Good, good, if you had
said something clever,
의심했을 수도 있어
she might've gotten suspicious.
Hey.
Hi.
쟤는 왜 왔어?
What's he doing here?
할 말이 있대
Okay, he wants
to talk to you.
난 얘기할 기분이 아냐
Well, I don't want
to talk to him.
너한테도 실망이다
And I'm pretty
disappointed in you, too.
오래가지는 않겠지만
Although we both
know that won't last.
할 말 있으면 해봐
Sheldon, you're up.
고마워
Thank you.
에이미, 사과하고 싶어
Amy, I'd like to apologize.
네 논문은 대단해
Your accomplishment
was impressive.
그리고 네가 자랑스러워
And I'm proud of you.
그건 코알라 볼 때
짓는 표정이잖아
We both know that's
your koala face.
내가 뭐랬어
I told you.
선물도 사왔어
Okay, look, he
bought you this.
보석?
Jewelry?
장난해?
Seriously?
쉘든,
넌 내가 아는 사람 중
Sheldon, you are
the most shallow,
제일 이기적인 놈이야
self-centered person
I have ever met.
내가 이런 뻔한 수작에...
Do you really think another
transparently manipul...
티아라다!
Oh, it's a tiara!
티아라!
A tiara!
I have a tiara!
씌워줘
Put it on me, put it on me,
put it on me, put it on me,
put it on me, put it
on me, put it on me.
아름답다
You look beautiful.
당연하지,
난 티아라를 쓴 공주야
Of course I do, I'm a princess,
and this is my tiara!
티아라는 좀 과했다
You were right,
the tiara was too much.
하워드,
베르나데트가...
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard! Bernadette's...
금방도 지나갔네
Oh, she slipped
right by me.
조끼 돌려줄게
Here's your vest back.
아냐, 너 가져
You should keep it.
언젠가 또 입을 수 있지
You could wear it
again sometime.
언제?
Where?
몰라, 사냥할 때?
I don't know, hunting?
나도 손주를 볼 수 있게
잘 좀 해결해봐
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Don't forget to talk to
her about this mishegas
where I don't
get grandkids!
걱정 마요
Don't worry, Ma.
민감한 주제지만
최선을 다할게요
I will, as soon
as I can figure out a way
to bring up
such a sensitive issue!
어머니께 말했어?
I guess you talked
to your mom, huh?
속상해서
I was upset.
엄마가 위로를
잘 해주거든
My mom can be a pretty
good shoulder to cry on,
엄마한테 로션 냄새가
나지만 참을만 해
if the smell of Bengay
doesn't burn your eyes.
너한테 아이가
정말 중요한 것 같아
Look, it's obvious having kids
is really important to you,
해결책을 생각했어
and I think I came up
with a solution.
정말?
(laughing):
Really?
뭔데?
That's great. What?
어차피 너보단
내가 더 많이 벌잖아
Well, seeing as how I make way
more money than you anyway,
내가 일을 하는 동안
네가 아이를 봐주는 거야
what if I work and you
stay home with the kids?
- 내가?
- 응
Me?
Yeah.
응, 같이 만화도 보고
You know, you'll watch Barney
마술도 보여주고
and pull Cheerios
out of their noses
다른 아이들이랑
놀면 재밌을 거야
and go on play dates,
나는 내 또래의 사람들과
어울리면서 인생을 즐길게
and I'll work and
have conversations
with people my own age
and enjoy my life.
응
Yeah...
그럼 됐지?
Yay, so we're good.
그래
Yeah, we're good.
따지고 보면
싸운 건 아니지만
You know, I don't know if
this counted as a fight,
화해로 섹스 어때?
but how about
some make-up sex?
좋지
I would love that.
어, 귀 뒤에 저건 뭐지?
But what is that
behind your ear?
콘돔이네
Oh, look, it's a condom.
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==